BU Records: Museum Studies Department, Inclusive: 1978-1997, undated, Bulk: 1990-1997
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Administrative Records, 1981-1997, undated; 2
  - Cultural Resource Management Program Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Evalution of Museum Studies Program, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Evaluation Criteria and Procedures, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Program Brochure, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Curriculum Hierarchy, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Program Admission Requirements, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Museum Studies Academic Program Goals Statement, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Resumes of Potential Visiting Lecturers, 1993-1995, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Student Handbooks from Other Academic Programs (1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Student Handbooks from Other Academic Programs (2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Student Advisory Sheets, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Anonymous Exit Interviews of Graduates, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Baylor Graduate School Memos and Mailings, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of Program (1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation of Program (2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Visiting Lecturers — Anne E. Worley, 1994-1996, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Catalog, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Graduate School Memos and Mailings, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Resumes of Regular Faculty, 1995, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Graduate School Memos and Mailings, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Center for Museum Studies, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Drafts of the Graduate Student Handbook, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Drafts of the Undergraduate Student Handbook, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Evaluation of Graduate Program by Dr. Jan Rosvall, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Curriculum Committee, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Faculty and Staff Retreat, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Policies and Procedures for the Musuem Studies Program by Susan Roth, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - MST 5323 - “Problems in Historic Preservation/Historical Administration” Historic Site Survey in Marlin, Texas., 1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Paid Advertisements, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Resumes of Graduate Adjunct Faculty, 1996, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Graduate School Memos and Mailings (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Graduate School Memos and Mailings (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies Student Association, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - T. Lindsey Baker — Program Committee for AASLH 1997 Annual Meeting (1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - T. Lindsey Baker — Program Committee for AASLH 1997 Annual Meeting (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Department Mission Statements, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Faculty and Staff Winter Retreat, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Entering Student Questionnaire, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Museum Studies Brochures, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Strecker Museum, 1978-1997, undated; 3
  This series contains materials related to the Strecker Museum such as financial records, materials related to donors, and materials related to museum accreditation. The series is in excellent condition.
  - Museum Association of Waco, 1978-1990 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Collection Care — Blast Freezing, 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Exhibits - SMEC, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Cambridge Seven Associates, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Strecker Museum Accreditation, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Strecker Associates, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Museums in South Africa, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - John K. Strecker Oral History Project, 1990, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Personal Policy, 1990, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Strecker Museum Finances (1 of 2), 1990-1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Strecker Museum Finances (2 of 2), 1990-1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - “Wilderness at Risk” by Glen L. Evans — Strecker Museum Occasional Paper (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - “Wilderness at Risk” by Glen L. Evans — Strecker Museum Occasional Paper (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Museum Training Affinity Group, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Public Relations, Undated (Box 28, Folder 12)